

tip_1_1_1=This is money - a very useful thing in this fairytale land. Collect all the coins and you earn extra points. Bigger coins are worth more points.
tip_1_1_2=Supercow can look down. To make her look down press the DOWN ARROW key or RIGHT MOUSE BUTTON. 
tip_1_1_3=You can jump into some of the wells. But jump at your own risk!
tip_1_1_4=Right you are! You can walk along roofs too.
tip_1_1_5=The most valuable thing you can find are hidden secrets. To find a secret you need to look really hard. 

tip_1_2_1=Be careful! Duriarti's creatures are everywhere! Try to jump on their heads.  
tip_1_2_2=Cleaning the environment is a very good thing for society, but it's a profitable thing to do too. Jump on the garbage and get extra points.
tip_1_2_3=This is a sleeping Déjà Vu mushroom. It's your assistant. If you wake the mushroom up, you can continue the game from this spot should you loose a life during this level. 
tip_1_2_4=This spring mattress can be useful if you don't have a place to sleep. It's also useful to jump on.
tip_1_2_5=If you think there might be something else on the other side of the exit, just run past it without stopping.

tip_1_3_1=This is an elevator. There are a lot of them in this fairytale land. There are some that just go up and down and others that wait until someone stands on them.
tip_1_3_2=A particularly secret secret is that Professor Duriarti has hidden his most valuable treasure. Discovering this secret is very lucky.
tip_1_3_3=The red heart is a very important prize. It re-energizes your health and gives you an extra life.
tip_1_3_4=A carton of super-milk improves your health.

tip_2_2_1=To neutralize some of your big, fat enemies you will to jump on them twice... or maybe even three times :)
tip_2_2_2=This is an apple tree. If you jump underneath it, you can collect some apples. Fruit is good for your health!

tip_2_3_1=On this level you must neutralize all of your enemies. Follow the arrow. If an enemy is close the arrow will change color. The counter in the upper left corner displays how many enemies you have remaining.
tip_2_3_2=The exit will open only after you have complete all the required tasks for the level: neutralize all your enemies.

tip_3_2_1=On this level you need to collect all of the keys before you can open the exit. Follow the green arrow and keep track of the mount of keys remaining to collect.
tip_3_2_2=Try to jump on a cloud!
tip_3_2_3=First complete the tasks for this level, then exit. Remember? :)

tip_4_1_1=There is liana to your right. You can swing on it by using the LEFT ARROW and RIGHT ARROW keys (or by moving your mouse).
tip_4_4_1=Now you get to meet a porcupine. You can neutralize him, when you have the hyper hoofs bonus. Don't try to jump on him without hyper hoofs. They are very prickly!!!

tip4_4_2=A cow with horseshoes hits his enemies two times harder. Don't miss the hyper-hoofs!


trophyname1=WINGED HOOFS
trophyname2=BAG OF MONEY
trophyname3=CHAMPAGNE
trophyname4=SUPER JUMP
trophyname5=THE OVERTHROWN PIG
trophyname6=THE OVERTHROWN GOAT
trophyname7=LAUREL WREATH
trophyname8=THE COW OF VENUS
trophyname9=RED CROSS
trophyname10=GOLDEN HORNS
trophyname11=THE TOKEN OF THE BEST DETECTIVE
trophyname12=THE UDDER CUP
trophyname13=BRONZE HORSEMAN

trophysubname1=a bronze sculpture
trophysubname2=about 100 million guilders from our sponsors
trophysubname3=the 1875 harvest, from bull fans
trophysubname4=a copper figurine
trophysubname5=a marble bust
trophysubname6=a bronze bust
trophysubname7=3 karat diamonds
trophysubname8=a 16 century work by Benvenuto Cellini
trophysubname9=a prize from Doctors Without Borders
trophysubname10=from our superhero colleagues
trophysubname11=from the FSB and CIA with love
trophysubname12=from the agriculture museum
trophysubname13=copper by an unknown Italian architect



willgettrophy=You were awarded this trophy
havegottrophy=You have this trophy

trophytip1=for three combos in a row
trophytip2=for collecting all the money on the level
trophytip3=for exceeding 100,000 points in the game
trophytip4=for six combos in a row
trophytip5=for defeating the first boss
trophytip6=for defeating the second boss
trophytip7=for exceeding 500,000 points in the game
trophytip8=for collecting all the valuables and coins, and getting rid of all the monsters on the leve
trophytip9=for completing the level without loosing any lives or health
trophytip10=for getting rid of all the monsters on this level
trophytip11=for discovering the 5th secret on this level
trophytip12=for collecting all of the valuables on this level
trophytip13=for defeating the most evil one

stage0= Supercow's landing point.
stage1= Molly the Sheep. Miss Sheep of Sunny Valley 2006. Supercow's best friend.
stage2= Jim the Donkey. Jolly guy who writes songs. Wants to be a pop star in the future.
stage3= Kevin the Goose. A real gentleman. He was born in Europe but has tendencies of getting involved in fraud.
stage4= Maggie the Chicken. Loves to cook, watch TV, and of course, sit on eggs.
stage5= Nick the Chick. Brave little fellow, who wants to be a superrooster when he grows up. He also wants to wear boots with spurs.
stage6= Mark the Rabbit. He's a scaredy cat, er... rabbit. But he's working on it. He's Sunny Valley's champion in eating cabbage.
stage7= Allie the Turkey. She bit of an odd duck, er... turkey. She enjoys Eastern religion and yoga.
stage8= Bob the Pig. He still isn't mature, and was a quite a hooligan when he was younger. Today he's an exemplary boar.
stage9= Roger the Goat. He doesn't like to sleep because it means he'll be separated from his motorcycle.
stage10= Bill the Bull. The farm executive director. He has known Supercow since his youth and really likes her.


edirotmode=EDITING MODE: F1 – EXIT THE EDITOR F2 – SAVE YOUR SETTINGS

modetip=Start the adventures!

optionstip=Volume, video, cursors.

infatip=Help, hi-score, etc.

exittip=Really wanna leave?

optionsync=Synchronizing can produce smoother image rendering in full screen mode, however it depends on the type of your video card. 





